



EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE / University of British Columbia

Post-Secondary

Fourth year student completing Bachelor of Science degree in Microbiology and Immunology Activities and Societies: Kappa Kappa Gamma, UBC Sororities, UBC Arbutus Collegia

BACHELOR OF ARTS / University of British Columbia

Post-Secondary

Fourth year student completing Bachelor of Arts degree in First Nations and Indigenous Studies.

DOGWOOD DIPLOMA / Crofton House School

Secondary

Acquired dogwood diploma with a 4.33 GPA. Activities and Societies: Assistant Head Girl (2015-2016).

Sept 2016 - Present

Sept 2016 - Present

Sept 2011 - Jun 2016

Mar 2018 - Present

WORK EXPERIENCE

PHARMACY ASSISTANT / London Drugs

Vancouver, BC

- Coordinated and collaborated to increase prescription count by 150% through enhanced customer service, strong and functional knowledge of healthcare, and efficient prescription processing and preparation.
- Developed interpersonal trust with Punjabi speaking patients. Effectively translated drug-related questions and counselled prescription from Punjabi to English-and viceversa-with credibility and confidence; growing the retention rate of the Punjabi client base two-fold.
- Effectively communicated and recruited customers to join London Drugs' rewards program, growing the regional client database by 5%.
- Displayed strong critical thinking and analytical skills to efficiently diagnose the status of patient medication in a fast paced and dynamic environment.

BOARD MEMBER / TELUS Vancouver Community Board

Sept 2016 - Sept 2019

Vancouver, BC

- Meticulously evaluated grant applications and facilitated the distribution of an annual \$1,000,000 fund by TELUS Vancouver to local, youth focused, grassroots initiatives in the Lower Mainland.
- Maintained a meaningful connection with awarded charities by conducting onsite visits and cheque presentations.

ADMINISTRATIVE ASSISTANT / Crofton House School

Jun 2016 - Feb 2018

Vancouver, BC

- Scheduled and coordinated appointments, tours, and interviews for prospective students easing the workload of the Admissions Department allowing for an increase in 25% more appointments.
- Used experimental technology for administrative support and data entry; doubled speed of information retrieval by eliminating unnecessary paperwork.
- Organized, distributed, and invigilated SSAT examinations while demonstrating high standards of professional conduct.

Profile

A creative and enthusiastic leader who is passionate about understanding places and the people within them; their culture, traditions, and experiences. Experienced working both in group environments and independently. A strong and motivated learner with excellent communication and organizational skills.



+1(604) 719-1946



jaujla@jastina.ca



7321 Inverness Street, Vancouver, BC, Canada



https://www.jastina.ca

<u>languages</u>

- English fluent
- Punjabi advanced
- French basic
- Mandarin novice

LEADERSHIP EXPERIENCE

SENIOR PROGRAM FACILITATOR / YWCA Metro Vancouver

Feb 2013 - Present

Vancouver, BC

- Proven leadership, communication, and problem-solving skills through 7 years of
 experience as a facilitator; inspiring over 400 at-risk youth to appreciate themselves
 and live a healthy and positive lifestyle.
- Excelled in **training**, **leading**, **and motivating newer volunteers** in developing their own facilitation and leadership skills by analyzing their areas of improvement, inspiring confidence, and cultivating a supportive environment that enabled meaningful growth.
- Fostered a collaborative and growth-friendly learning environment by turning conflicts into teachable moments through skills acquired by attending annual facilitation and communication workshops.

VP MEMBERSHIP EXPERIENCE / UBC Sororities

Nov 2017 - Nov 2018

Vancouver, BC

- Developed new programming for 800+ members alongside the Sexual Assault Support Centre (SASC) and Sexual Violence and Prevention Response Office (SVPRO) to educate our members on bystander intervention and disclosure training.
- Established the organization's first Sexual Violence and Prevention Response Action
 Plan in support with the University of British Columbia (UBC), SASC, and SVPRO;
 providing necessary support and accommodations to any member that reports an
 incident of such nature.
- Facilitated community-wide cooperation promoting harmony and teamwork. Acted as a liaison between the UBC community members, UBC administration and Inter-Fraternity Council to identify and address key concerns within UBC Greek Life.

EXECUTIVE POSITIONS

BOARD SECRETARY / DTES Neighbourhood House

Jun 2020 - Present

Vancouver, BC

• Experienced incoming board member elected on to the Board's executive team to improve organization, governance, and achieve long term goals.

YOUTH ADVISOR / RCMP Youth Advisory Committee

Oct 2019 - Present

Vancouver, BC

- Represented the national youth voice in topics of crime and victimization, such as sexual consent, cyberbullying, and cannabis legalization, as **one of 40 youth** across Canada.
- Increased adoption of the RCMP's educational resources by over 600 school boards through collaboration in bi-weekly conversations to develop effective youth strategies.

CHAIR AND SECRETARY / London Drugs Action Committee

Mar 2018 - Present

Vancouver, BC

- Resolved 90% of matters related to employee concerns and disputes through consistent advocacy and communication between departments and management.
- Cultivated a **strong company culture** by collaborating with a highly motivated team to organize store-wide volunteer events and fundraisers to support staff functions.

COLLEGIATE ADVISOR / Kappa Kappa Gamma Advisory Committee Oct 2018 - Oct 2019 Vancouver, BC

- One of 12 collegiate members and the only Canadian chapter representative selected from across North America to improve the Fraternity's operation and structure.
- Collaborated with collegians to evaluate the Fraternity's initiatives to improve the collegiate experience for active members.

PROJECTS

CO-FOUNDER / JAJU

Mar 2020 - Present

Vancouver, BC

 Passion project to market and create an online presence for small businesses during the COVID-19 pandemic.